

**Víctor** Morais Llahi

**DATE OF BIRTH:** 07/03/1999

### CONTACT

Nationality: Spanish

Gender: Male

C/ Provença 155 3° 2°, 08036 Barcelona, Spain



(+34) 629189608

# **ABOUT ME**

Having finished my studies as a graduate in computer engineering, I aspire to climb another step and deepen my knowledge even more. At the same time, I would also be interested in starting to gain experience in the world of work because I am one of those who believe that there is no better way to learn than with practice. I compensate my lack of professional experience in the sector with my determination and my ability to work both individually and collectively. I am an open, sociable person, with very good public speaking and, above all, with ability both in leadership and in being led. Among my personal hobbies I highlight sports, mainly swimming because I have been underwater for more than twelve years, and writing novels of all genres in which to free my imagination.

# **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**2021 – CURRENT** – Edifici B6 del Campus Nord, C/Jordi Girona, 1-3 Barcelona España, Barcelona, Spain

# Master in Computer Engineering

Facultad de Informática de Barcelona - Universidad Politécnica de Catalunya

https://www.fib.upc.edu/es

**2017 - 2021** - Edifici B6 del Campus Nord, C/Jordi Girona, 1-3, Barcelona, Spain

# Degree in Computer Engineering

Facultad de Informática de Barcelona - Universidad Politécnica de Catalunya

Taking a degree in computer engineering has allowed me to acquire the necessary knowledge to conceive, design, develop, maintain and manage computer systems, services, applications and architectures, to know and apply the necessary legislation, as well as to gain experience in new methods and technologies of the ICT field. Among the five branches in which a graduate can specialize during this degree, I have chosen software engineering, thus deepening my knowledge in the creation of software systems that respond to the needs of users and companies, reliable and efficient, and to manage to the people, resources and stages of the project from the definition of the client's needs to the construction and deployment of the system.

## Field(s) of study

Computer Engineering - Specialization in Software Engineering
Final grade: 7 | yayOS: Interactive web application to learn how to use a computer for elderly people | <a href="https://www.fib.upc.edu/es">https://www.fib.upc.edu/es</a>

### 2016 - 2017

Participation in the Xarxa Vives Secondary and High School Debate Leagues.

Universidad de Barcelona

#### 2015 - 2015

Participation in the 1st edition of the Robotics Course of the Scientific and Technological Summer Campus Program

Instituto de Ciencias de la Educación de la Universidad Politécnica de Catalunya

#### 2015 - 2015

Participation in the 6th edition of the Ramón Valldeoriola y Soler Awards for Excellence in ESO

Institución Sant Josep

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

03/09/2018 - CURRENT - Barcelona, Spain

#### Leisure monitor

Plus Arts

- Activity monitor.
- Animator of children's parties.
- Equipment maintenance.
- Watchman of attractions.
- Responsible manager.

2016 - 2018 - Barcelona, Spain

#### Math tutor

I was a private teacher of mathematics for students who were in compulsory secondary school. Although I primarily taught math, I also did physics, chemistry, and technology.

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Castellano / Catalán / Portugués

**OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** 

Inglés

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
C1	C1	production	interaction	C1
		C1	C1	

# DIGITAL SKILLS

# In computers

C++ / Python / React / Hardware notions / IntelliJ IDEA / Github y Bitbucket / Java / CSS / HTML / Agile Methodologies (Scrum, Kanban) / #C / Word, Pdf, PowerPoint, Excell / Adobe XD / JSX / SmallTalk / Basics in databases / Trello / Git / JSON / JavaScript

#### Work methodology

Sustainability analysis / Team work / Proactivity and leadership / Rigor in validation / Responsibility at work / Temporary planning / Analysis of the functional and non-functional requirements of a system / Knowledge of the code of ethics / Experience in project presentations

### Academic projects carried out to highlight

Recreation of Hacker News web / QOE Meter: Quality of Experience Analyzer for mobiles (collaboration with Telefónica) / Pockles: geosocial network for mobiles / Study on COVID19 Tracking Apps and Privacy / Tra ffic sign detection algorithm